

Saba Katsadze

Date of birth: 12/12/1999

Nationality: Georgian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Glasgow G72 8UR Glasgow, United Kingdom (Home)

katsadzesaba2@gmail.com

(+44) 07519297404

https://ss19991212.github.io/ Saba CV.github.io/

https://www.facebook.com/ saba.kacadze.7

© 07519297404 (WhatsApp)



ABOUT ME

Driven and tenacious young professional from Georgia. With a bachelor's degree in International Relations. Currently pursuing a Master's degree in Central and East European, Russian and Eurasian studies through the Erasmus Mundus Joint Master's Degree program. I have a diverse range of internship experiences. My professional background includes a role at US Embassy in Tbilisi, at Public Affairs Section, internship in the department of Planning, Research and International Relations at the National Center of Education Quality Enhancement of Georgia and at the Communications Department at the Administration of the President of Georgia. These experiences have provided me with valuable insights into public relations, communications and strategic-planning.

Recently I have started expanding my skillset and have become interested in the promising field of Digital Marketing. I have obtained the certificate from Google's Digital Garage, Digital Marketing course, alongside Coursera's Specialization in SEO course. As well as Codeacademy's certificate of HTML/CSS to complement my SEO skills. Currently I am studying Google Analytics and plan to improve my data analysis and market research skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

30/06/2020 - 22/01/2021 Tbilisi, Georgia

Intern of the Public Affairs Secion United States Embassy in Georgia

Member of the Press Team. Mainly tasked with preparing daily news reports, translating and preparing transcripts.

01/09/2021 - 10/01/2022 Georgia

Intern of the Planning, Research and International Relations Department LEPL National Center for Education Quality Enhancement

Mainly tasked with double-checking, reviewing and translating documents, as well as assisting other members of the team in executing day-to-day tasks.

22/12/2021 - 03/2022 Tbilisi, Georgia

Intern of the Communications Office Administration of the President of Georgia

Monitoring political trends domestically and abroad. Working on President's visibility through website and social media management. Preparing daily news reports and assisting the staff in administrative duties.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

08/09/2023 - CURRENT Glasgow, United Kingdom

International Master's in Central and East European, Russian and Eurasian Studies Tartu, Glasgow & Jagiellonian Universities

03/10/2018 - 05/2022

Student Caucasus University

Address 1 Paata Saakadze Street | Website https://cu.edu.ge/

Delegate at European School of Policy and Reforms Konr ad Adenauer Stiftung

Website https://www.kas.de/de/home

Delegate at Global Challenges Forum 2019 Future Diplomats' Club Website https://www.facebook.com/FutureDiplomatsClub/ Certificate of Participation in the Yearly Student Conference - 2021 Caucasus University Website https://cu.edu.ge/ Certificate of Participation in the Essay competition of "NATO, Georgia and Current Security Challenges: The 2018 Brussels Summit And Beyond" Embassy of Bulgaria Website https://www.mfa.bg/en/embassies/georgia **United Kingdom** Certificate of SEO Coursera Website Coursera.org **United Kingdom Certificate of Google's Digital Marketing Course** Google Website Google.com **United Kingdom HTML & CSS Certificate** CodeAcademy Website Codeacademy.com LANGUAGE SKILLS MOTHER TONGUE(S): Georgian Other language(s): **English** Listening C2 Spoken production C1 Reading C2 Spoken interaction C1 Writing C1 Russian **Listening** B1 Spoken production B1 **Reading B1** Spoken interaction B1 Writing B1 **French** Listening A2 Spoken production A2 Spoken interaction A2 Reading A2 Writing A2 Spanish Listening A2 Spoken production A2 **Reading** A2 Spoken interaction A2

Writing A2

Polish

Listening A1 Spoken production A1
Reading A1 Spoken interaction A1
Writing A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Basic Digital Marketing \mid Basic Knowledge of SEO \mid Copywriting (basic) \mid HTMI & CSS \mid Google (Google Ads, Google Analytics) \mid Microsoft Excel